

Shahriyar Tarnasi

C# | Python Programmer

DoB: 1994-05-03 Marital Status: Single Military Service: Medical Exemption

Profile Summary

I love programming, this is just beginning of my journey. I want to be a specialist and trusted guy how doing his job perfectly. I like structural code and good architecture, It is a thing i will try for .)

Contact



shahryar.tarnasi@gmail.com



(+1)+1(954) 281-2703



+989192625011



https://shahriyartarnasi.site



dehghan villa, Karaj, Alborz, Iran

Skills

C#



Python



ASP.NET Core



Django



ASP.NET Core API

Education

Bachelor of Information Technology

Branch: Web Development Institute/University: elmi karbordi Karaj, Alborz, Iran 2014 - 2018

Work Experience

Co-Founder | Lead Backend Technology

Saxon Drilling

Business Bay, Dubai, United Arab Emirates (UAE)

June 2022 - Present

Tasks and Achievements

- Sy stem Design
- Microservice architecture
- W orking with complicated Flows and a lot of odds (connections and relations)
- Testing (UnitTest, Load Test)

Python | Django Developer

Fibodex

Karaj, Alborz, Iran

April 2021 - Present

Tasks and Achievements

- Celerv
- Scheduler (Celery Beat)
- WebSocket (Channels Django WebSockets PY Socket IO)
- relations and motivation in management colleges
- Authentication and Authorization (JWT, Oauth2, Google OAuth)

Python | Django Developer

Travel Agency Azade

Karaj, Alborz, Iran

January 2019 - May 2020

Tasks and Achievements

- REST API
- Dashboard (HTML to dy namic W ebsite)
- Authentication (Cookie, Session)

Python | Django Developer

ICS

Tehran, Iran

May 2020 - September 2020

Tasks and Achievements

- Dashboard CRM
- Complication Flows
- Refactoring
- Testing Code

